





M @joãoteixeira96

https://github.com/joaoteixeira96



Cybersecurity

# tryhackme.com/p/JooTeixeira | top 5% 🗘 🏗 app.hackthebox.com/profile/188011

#### **PROFILE**

Since I was a kid, I always wanted to catch bad guys, but in a smart way! So cybersecurity was the deal. I'm a curious person with team spirit, openminded and eager to learn, having several years of experience in programming and security gained through personal, academic, and company projects. Looking for a role where I can grow and continue to learn from experienced people.

#### EDUCATIONAL

#### **NOVA College of Science and Technology**

Master of Science in Computer Science.

• Attended from Sept. 2019 to Sept. 2021, specializing in computer network, system security and distributed systems.

#### **NOVA College of Science and Technology**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science.

• Attended from Sept. 2015 to April 2019.

#### SKILLS

## **Knowledge Areas**

- Vulnerability Management.
- Risk Assessment.
- Application Security.

#### **Programming/Web Development**

• Java, Python, SQL, C#, Kotlin, JavaScript/ReactJS, HTML/CSS.

#### Tools/Frameworks/CTF

• Kali linux, Metasploit, Nessus, BurpSuite, Nmap, ZAP, Wireshark, John, Hydra, sqlmap, TOR, Docker, Azure, Git, OWASP, NIST, OSSTMM, MITRE ATT&CK.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Security Delivery Associate**

Accenture Portugal | July 2021 to present.

- Vulnerability Management
  - Assess, validate the risk and prioritize remediation of the vulnerabilities.
  - Coordinate responsibilities with the different project teams.
  - Create a monthly executive report.
- Application Security
  - Application testing and conducting security assessment for web applications using SCA, SAST and DAST scan tools & manual penetration
  - Executive report & presentation of the findings.
- MSS Support client customers to assess, protect, detect and respond to their solutions.
- · Assist in the analysis of security requirements in RFP documents.

# **Full Stack Developer Intern**

EInnovator - Enterprise Middleware, LTD | Out. 2018 to Feb. 2019.

- Developed a microservice solution using Spring Framework that allowed companies and employees to review, edit or revoke product contracts.
- Agile methodology (Jira).

#### Member of the organization committee

NLNF - FCT NOVA IT Club | Set. 2018 to Jul. 2019.

• Organized Talks, Workshops and a 2-day Hackathon.

#### Member of the organization committee

JORTEC - FCT NOVA IT | Set. 2017 to Jul. 2018.

• Organized Workshops and a 3-day Hackathon.

# **PROJECTS**

# Thesis – Strengthening of Tor Against Traffic Correlation with K-Anonymity Input Circuits

 Built a mechanism to protect Tor users against traffic correlation attacks, using combined techniques: Kanonymity routing strategy and overlaying traffic morphing